I am very happy to be able to share with you some of our discussions about the future development direction and possibilities in the digital fashion field, and I am also very grateful for the invitation of the organizer.
The topic I am going to share with you today is about the imagination of digital fashion, and the moderator just introduced it to me, so I won't go into too much detail about it.
Our course is actually a special design course for the third grade of the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts, and it is also the first time for the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts to open a fashion design school in recent years.
It is also the first time for the Chinese Academy of Fine Arts to open a fashion design school in recent years.
In this course, the students do not have any software-based skills.
In the previous period, they did not have any courses related to software.
This course is about seven weeks long.
How to guide students in this limited time of seven weeks?
It is a relatively big problem for us to create a multi-dimensional project based on these software-based students.
In addition, we are designing the initial design of this course.
This course is about the core problems of the first period of the course, which is the possibility of digitalization in the future of the fashion field.
It is a very mature and widely used app.
We would like to combine these digitalized, virtual, and different directions to explore whether there are more possibilities in addition to virtual fashion, virtual showrooms, or commercial brands.
In addition, we chose to use this kind of teamwork to teach the form and the problems that appear in our entire work flow and work process.
First of all, we lead students to learn about the historical origins of digital fashion, cultural evolution, technical development, and the impact of artificial intelligence on the trend of fashion in the future,
and to open up the imagination of students in the information age and a new understanding of fashion design.
This course is to break down the concepts of digitalized media and the real physical world,
and to make digitalized fashion design into an imaginative collection for students,
and to systematically establish the creative thinking logic of students' personal digitalized fashion design,
and to complete the digitalized fashion series and the display of digitalized application scenarios in the form of collaborative cooperation by learning from the software mentioned earlier.
Then we can first introduce a relatively more complete presentation of the final work of this group.
Hey, is there a sound?
A sound world.
Are there any things one can 있算s of this work?
How can what one is seeing be seen in what's happening in the present?
Buh-bye, Bowie.
will be more targeted to help students complete their projects.
In the process of learning software,
we will also integrate this kind of one-to-one counseling form.
Me and Percy, we mainly go to
the project development of the students
and the final form and content produced by them.
Then, at the end of the final presentation in the seventh week,
we held a small exhibition in the school.
Some groups focused more on food interaction,
while others focused more on virtual interaction.
In the video we just saw,
they focused more on virtual interaction
and presented different forms of content produced for different projects.
These are some of our teachers.
They are all
artists and professional designers
who have been growing in the fashion industry for many years.
Percy is a modern and advanced digital artist.
He is mainly responsible for the teaching of AIGC and Nomad.
Yaya created a brand called Elter,
which is a virtual fashion brand.
At the time, it was in VVS Westwood,
the design headquarters in London,
and it was designed by a 3D fashion designer.
He also landed virtual fashion in the industry,
whether it is in his own brand
or in the current luxury brand,
and he is a designer who has the industry experience
to really land in the industry.
Then, Mr. Qi Haoran is a teacher
who is biased towards this C4D scene modeling direction,
and Mr. Maruyama is responsible for the interaction direction.
Because in each project,
we actually have this kind of interaction with each other.
This kind of interaction with each other,
this kind of interaction with people,
this kind of inter-application application,
and then, Mr. Ma has had
this kind of interaction teaching experience for nearly 10 years.
Then, in our entire interaction teaching process,
he replied that there are a lot of problems
that he has not encountered in his teaching in so many years.
Because our students,
they have no basis for these software,
so they
do not have a limit or prediction
that what they can do,
what they cannot do.
So, the whole thing is that
when they are imagining,
it is their final output as a guide,
and then the teachers,
according to the effect they want,
to carry out this software support teaching.
Then, this is when we first started the class,
it is actually equivalent to a very big lecture,
and then each teacher will take their own,
this is the field of deep learning for many years,
some of the things that are happening at the moment,
and the possibility of this kind of development in the future,
to do a lecture.
Then, this is a mini project part of our first week,
that is, some of the projects they produced
after a week of software learning.
Then, the next is this group project part,
that is, teamwork.
First of all,
why do we use this group project?
Why do we use this group,
or teamwork in this form?
The first one is that
the objective condition limitation mentioned earlier,
is that the students have no basis for this software,
and the students actually do not have this equipment
to carry out this,
to carry out that,
that is, especially like rendering this part.
Then, in the whole process of their production,
there are students,
in order to do this rendering,
they may go to this,
his friend's game company,
because they have that computer,
and then it is relatively professional
and the computer with a higher configuration,
and then borrow their computer,
to do this later rendering,
and then in the middle,
there have been a lot of,
that is, this kind of situation
of suddenly retreating,
and then another one is,
for this kind of future social skills,
a preview,
for example,
how they are going to deal with
the situation of interpersonal relationships
in various kinds of this kind of teamwork,
that is, how to maximize their personal value
and the value of the team,
that is, sometimes,
because you may encounter,
for example,
your personal ideas
need to serve this team,
you need to get,
that is,
to achieve a certain compromise and balance,
and then,
that is,
how do you find your own role in the team,
and so on,
and then,
including them,
they may encounter some,
for example,
that is,
there are some members of the team,
lack of certain skills,
that is,
maybe they are not very good at this software learning application,
and that is,
may encounter,
that is,
some groups will involve this programming part,
that they do not have this,
that is,
students who are good at programming,
that may need them to change this,
the final production form,
and then there are some,
that is,
may not be very good at digitalization,
this part,
that their team's plan will involve,
for example,
producing some clothing food,
in this kind of food,
that is,
the interaction between the food and people at the scene,
and then,
there is also,
that is,
we encountered a problem in this group project,
because we invited some industries,
that is,
there are their own companies,
or their own projects,
or their own brand mentors,
that they sometimes have no way,
to really go to the scene to teach,
that is,
will take this form of online teaching,
including in the early stages of this course,
we made a,
online resource arrangement,
that is,
will give students some,
this online course link,
then students can themselves,
that is,
mobilize their subjective energy,
to do this software learning,
and then,
there is,
that is,
we are going to do that,
when the whole project is guided,
that is,
a core point I discussed with Professor Percy,
in this virtual world,
this digital world,
is different from the real world,
that is,
it has no limitation,
it is for this real world,
this view of the world,
and the structure of the world,
that is,
it can have a subversive design,
hope students to spread their own,
that is,
spread their own imagination and creativity,
to create a new,
a new view of the world,
and the structure of the world,
and then,
this is,
that is,
at the beginning,
we saw that video,
a presentation of a project,
of their team,
that is,
what he did,
is about this upside-down world,
made a world,
opposite to the real world,
a upside-down world,
and then,
this is his previous research,
that is,
about,
some of the meanings of the upside-down,
the explanation,
and then,
some of,
And this is a draft of the design of the whole computer world at the time.
It's like a multi-dimensional cube.
Because there are four students, they made four rooms, and each room has its own story.
And these are the designs of the students on virtual clothing.
You can see that each student has a very strong personality.
This is the room of the first student.
She is a sensitive and warm-hearted girl.
She does things related to her childhood and family.
Then,
in terms of clothing, she mainly applies the technology of Qo3D.
And this is the second part of the clothing.
The third student's clothing.
And this is the design of each room.
They have two different works for hand- студents.
The first one is very unique.
This is the figure of the second student.
And the second one, the figure of the third student.
This is the figure of the third student.
And this is the figure of the fourth student.
The third student is very active.
This is the figure of the fourth student.
And this is the figure of the final student.
然后这个是他们现场的一些就是食物交互的部分
就是我们可以看到就是前面有一个就是观众在挥手嘛
他在挥手的时候这个投影到这个服装和场景上面的这个纹样
是随着这个手的动作在变化
然后右边这个呢他其实做了一个小的这种互动的配饰和装置
就是当然人的就是这个这个就是他的这个灯光的流速和快慢会随着
就是你触摸到他会感应到你心心跳心率的变化而去变化他的速度
就这个这个我就没有再放视频了
然后这个呢是另一组
同学作品
嗯然后接下来是一个大的相当于每个项目的一个概览吧像第一个就是跟这个喔就是来就维度 这一组就是跟那个传统的这种文样与现在的这种交互的形式相结合那我们看到下面诗诟地就最左边这个下面诗读的就是什么样的相似的相向结合那我们看到下面诗读的就是 overcoming诗读是一样的形式像标 extremely
我们看到下面诗读的就 organisation
iping
It's actually more of an application of AIGC, which is Stable Diffusion's software, to do some training and production.
It's like every student using their own drawing and design to build their own database.
Then Stable Diffusion uses its own style to generate more possibilities for design.
And then the one in the middle is the analysis of the case we started to do.
It's more of a purely virtual history and virtual interaction part.
Then the two groups on the right, the group above, is the interaction device we just started to share,
which is the interaction device related to heart rate.
And then the group below applies a kind of 3D projection and virtual generation interaction direction design.
Thank you!